<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Astronomy Pictures</string>
    <string name="today_screen">Today</string>
    <string name="collection_screen">Collection</string>
    <string name="details_screen">Details</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="application_info">This application based on APOD API.</string>
    <string name="apod">"Astronomy Picture of the Day "</string>
    <string name="apod_info_1">Astronomy Picture of the Day (APOD) is originated, written, coordinated, and edited in 1995, 1996, 1997, and 1998 by Robert Nemiroff and Jerry Bonnell. The APOD archive contains the largest collection of annotated astronomical images on the internet.</string>
    <string name="apod_info_2">In real life, Bob and Jerry are two professional astronomers who spend most of their time researching the universe. Bob is an assistant professor at Michigan Technological University in Houghton, Michigan, USA, while Jerry is a scientist at NASA\'s Goddard Space Flight Center in Greenbelt, Maryland USA. They are two married, mild, and lazy guys who might otherwise appear normal to an unsuspecting guest. Together, they have found new and unusual ways of annoying their wives such as staging astronomical debates. Most people are surprised to learn that they have developed the perfect random number generator.</string>
    <string name="apod_info_3">APOD is proud to acknowledge that it received several accolades during its short existence. In 1994, APOD was voted NASA\'s Cool Site of the Year. In 1996, APODs popularity rose to make it among the most popular astronomy sites on the web. In 1997 and 1998, APOD was mentioned among PC Magazine\'s Top 100 Web Sites.</string>
    <string name="about_image_permissions">About image permissions</string>
    <string name="permissions_details">All the images on the APOD page are credited to the owner or institution where they originated. Some of the images are copyrighted and to use these pictures publicly or commercially one must write to the owners for permission. For the copyrighted images, the copyright owner is identified in the APOD credit line (please see the caption under the image), along with a hyperlink to the owner\'s location. NASA images are in the public domain, official guidelines for their use can be found here. For images credited to other owners/institutions, please contact them directly for copyright and permissions questions.</string>
    <string name="copyright">"Copyrigth: "</string>
    <string name="explanation">Explanation:</string>
    <string name="appwidget_text">EXAMPLE</string>
    <string name="configure">Configure</string>
    <string name="add_widget">Add widget</string>
    <string name="app_widget_description">This is an app widget description</string>
    <string name="corner_size">Corner size:</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="random">Random</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="system">System</string>
    <string name="lock_screen">Lock screen</string>
    <string name="system_and_lock_screen"><![CDATA[System & Lock screen]]></string>
    <string name="set_wallpaper">set wallpaper</string>
    <string name="share_image">share image</string>
    <string name="open_image_description">open image description</string>
    <string name="copied_to_clipboard">Copied to clipboard</string>

<!--    Settings-->
    <string name="back">back</string>
    <string name="no_description">no description</string>
    <string name="setting_description">$s. $s.</string>
<!--    Appearance-->
    <string name="appearance">Appearance</string>
    <string name="theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="light_theme">Light</string>
    <string name="dark_theme">Dark</string>
    <string name="system_theme">System</string>
</resources>